classroomclipart.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy

> > > Classroom Clipart has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Classroom Clipart.Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Classroom Clipart web site contains links to other sites. **Classroom Clipart** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.   
>                   
>>> 
>>> **What We Collect and How We Use It**
>>> 
>>> Anybody can access Classroom Clipart . We do not collect more personally identifiable information than necessary to participate in any of the site's activities, and we do not sell or transfer any personally identifiable information collected at this site to third parties. 
>>> 
>>> **Policies for Individuals Under 13**
>>> 
>>> **Classroom Clipart** encourages parents and guardians to spend time  online with their children and to participate in the interactive  activities offered on the sites. No information should be submitted to or posted at Classroom Clipart guests under 13 years of age without the consent of   their parent or guardian.  Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, Classroom Clipart does not  provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. No information collected from guests under 13 years of age is used  for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever Guests' e-mail addresses are never posted on Classroom Clipart site.
>>> 
>>> **About IP Addresses**
>>> 
>>> Classroom Clipart collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. AIP address is a number that's assigned to your computer   whenever you're log onto your ISP to surf the Web.    Our servers log the IP address of our guest. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that when you are logged on, your identity remains anonymous to us.          
>>> 
>>> **Use of Cookies -- Classroom Clipart Online Cookies Policy**
>>> 
>>> What is a cookie? A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. However, at this time., Classroom Clipart does not use cookies to track ANY user information. No cookies are used by Classroom Clipart. 
>>> 
>>>   
>  **Third Party Advertising**  
>  We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). You may Opt-Out of online behavorial advertisements by visiting [Network Advertisement Initiative. ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)You may also read more about protecting your privacy at Network Advertising Initiative website. 
>>> 
>>> ###  Newsletter Opt-Out  policy
>>> 
>>> Classroom Clipart offer a free electronic newsletter to users.  Classroom Clipart gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove  themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
